this meeting so it's gonna be out of order tonight but we'll call to order the regular
scouting meeting of my city council for tuesday may 19th 2026 item two in public input unscheduled
personal appearances we have none 3a claims list most to approve second all right all right
aye 3b minutes from the may 5th 2026 regular meeting most to approve
aye 3c fireworks production contract with schneider's fireworks an importing company
for the july 4th event held at buffalo run casino and event center not exceed $20,000 is that
yep this so this is the annual show that we partner with buffalo run so this is just to
approve the contract between us and schneider's to shoot those off again this year make motion
to approve second aye 3d memorandum of understanding with the witty enterprises
warehouse evangelism for the community garden project located at 201l southeast and 207l
authorized city manager to sign and also zip so this is a an mou between us and witty
enterprises the warehouse evangelism these are located on a couple of lots we have over on
l street southeast this is a project that was started last year it did get started due to
some issues that he had it kind of slowed down but he is still interested in doing it
nothing's changed we just extended it out for another year for him to see if he can
do this it's going to be a community garden and things as such so was this the location where
he was like mowing yes everything yes ma'am so everything will stay the same as far as his
upkeep and his expectation ours will be the same as well and like i said he he had some
health issues he had a knee he had every place so slowed him down but he's still
on board and ready to continue with it this quick question misty this is still city
property right yes are we so liable if there's any accidents it arguably yeah i mean there are
i mean does this memorandum protect us against that if something happened we would be a named
party certainly right i don't know that i don't know that we would well given that all they're
doing is gardening it's probably not a high risk anyway just a curious question we could be
okay can we get at probably not if it's our if it's property that we own
but that's what our big insurance policies for so we have insurance in the company yes
yes and mr witty also provides liability insurance as well as part of this
thank you we're a named party to his insurance motion to approve second
uncle all right hi hi item four other new business if any which has risen since
the posting of this agenda five staff reports six mayor council community announcements
last week again we missed police week national police week i want to thank the
miama police department and all the surrounding police departments in the area
for the outstanding job that they do in our community and everything that they do for us
thank you chief and for your department seven city manager communications yes sir eight
motion